long time no see.
久しぶり
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
It's gotten even cuter again.
なんかまた一段と可愛くなったね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Are you doing something?
なんかやってんの?
Are you doing it?
やってる?
Or did you start watching it after that?
とか、あれから見ようとか始めたの?
a little bit.
ちょっと
That's right.
そうね
Beautiful.
きれいな
I mean, my outfit today is cute.
てか俺がね、今日の服装、可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It was cute last time too.
前 回も可愛かったけど
What do you mean?
なんか その、なんていうの?
Do you have clothes like this?
こういう感じの服装ですみたいなのあるの?
Something inside me wasn't set up though.
その自分の中でなんか、設置じゃないけど
I think it's quite common though.
結構いっさせるなって思うけど
Well, that's not a quick answer.
え、ちょっと、速答じゃないんですけど
Was it fluffy?
ふわっきしてたの?
Isn't it fluffy?
ふわっきしてない?
It's not fluffy.
ふわっきしてない
Well then, just have sex with me last time.
じゃあちょっと、前回もエッチしてさ
Listen everyone, are you naughty?
みなさん聞いて、エッチなの?
picture?
え?
Enkai.
えんかい
Well, I'll just ask you this first,
じゃあこっちだけさ、最初に聞いちゃうけど、
Sex
エッチ
of.
を
It's situational.
シ チュエーション的なさ
It makes me excited.
キュンキュンするよな
Like flirting.
イチャイチャみたいな
Come on, have you ever had sex?
なんかさ、出せ、エッチとかしたことあるの?
Will it be captured on camera?
カメラに撮られるの?
You said it was your first time last time.
前回初めてって言ってたじゃん
Other than being photographed, are there any hens?
撮られる以外で、はめんどりとかいない?
What is SM?
SMとか何?
Any questions?
質問ない?
How much?
多少は?
Are you somewhat interested?
多少興味ある?
Are you interested in Curtainch?
カーテンチ興味ある?
In the car or something.
車の中とか
It's a little scary in the car.
車の中ちょっと怖いな
Is it a little scary?
ちょっと怖いか
I'm not an SM person, but are you interested in Curtainch?
SMじゃないけど、カーテンチの興味ある?
How much?
多少は?
Can I have it done?
やってもらっていい?
I would like to try it for a while.
ちょっとしてみたいかな
Anyway, today is also a different kind of sex, a different kind of sex.
一応今日も変わったエッチ、変わったエッチなのよ
Last time I was holding my camera,
前回の僕が、自分のカメラを持ちながら、
Nozuku looks like a hen.
のづくにはめんどりみたいな
Things have changed.
変 わったじゃん
It doesn't change much, but it's not me.
あんまり変わんないんだけど、 僕じゃなくて、
I prepared another man.
別の男を用意した
good.
いい
This may be bad, but
これは、これは悪いかもしれないですけど、
I showed you how addicted I was,
僕がはめのりしたのを見せちゃったんだけど、
Inに
Ciに
It was just there.
別にそこだけだったんです
I showed it to you.
見せちゃったんです
I think it's really cute.
めっちゃ可愛いじゃん、みたいな
I want to meet you.
会いたいと
I want to have sex with you.
俺のエッチしたい
We had a fight.
喧嘩したんだけど
We had a fight with my woman, but I'm going to let her go no matter what.
俺の女で喧嘩したんだけど、 どうしてもとどけさせるから
I read it.
読んじゃったんだけど
good?
いい?
Well then...
じゃあ、 その ...
Which child...
ど この子で...
Rare showman...
レアショーマン...
Easy.
簡単に
So, I'm also interested in something a little different.
じゃあ、ちょっと変わったやつも興味あると
Which one do you like?
どっちが好き?
どっちが好きだ?
I agree.
そうですね
Don't let me run away.
逃がさないで、俺は
I'm going to dig deeper into that.
深掘りしていくよ、そういうとこ
Well, I'd like to ask you some questions.
じゃあ、いろいろ聞きたいんだけど、
Is there such a thing as a sex fleet?
もうちょっと、性艦隊とかってあるの?
Is there one?
あるの?
Wait, which sex fleet?
てか、どこの性艦隊?
That's true.
それはあるよね
Where is the sex fleet?
性艦隊ってどこ?
Where is it?
どこだろう?
When you say "see", do you pick it up?
シーって言うとピックアップすると?
Where is it?
どこだろう?
Does it feel good to be licked?
舐められるの気持ちいいの?
like?
好き?
Where does it feel good to be licked?
どこ舐められた気持ちいいの?
Else.
他に
What do you mean if you can't answer?
答えられないとこってこと?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Does that mean it's not possible?
できないところってことかな?
it is.
それは
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいな
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Well then, you don't have to say it.
じゃあさ、 口で言わなくていいから
Wait a minute, hurry up.
ちょっと待って、早く
Stop.
停止して
Where is that?
そこってどこだろう?
feet?
足?
where?
どこ?
What do you say?
なんて言うの?
There?
そこ?
chestnut?
栗?
chestnut.
栗
Around here.
この辺
chestnut?
栗?
Does it feel good not to turn into a chestnut?
栗にならないと気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
So, Kuri, how does it feel to be licked?
じゃあ栗は、 どういう風に舐められた気持ちいいの?
Licking it.
ペロペロって
What is Peropero?
ペ ロペロって?
Is that licking hard?
それは激しくペロペロって?
Or lick it loosely?
それとも緩くペロペロ?
loosely?
緩く?
Licking it
ペロペロと、 す
Mare.
ま れ
Chestnut feels so good, I want you to lick it.
気持ちいい栗、 ペロペロしてほしい
Do I have to say it?
言 わなきゃダメですか?
I told him that chestnut felt so good, so I wanted him to lick it.
栗が気持ちいいから、 ペロペロしてほしいですって言って
Because chestnuts feel good.
栗が気持ちいいから
Raw liver chestnut.
生肝体栗です
What do you do?
何がするの?
I'll listen to that too.
そこも聞きます
Are you hearing something strange?
何か変なこと聞いてる?
behind.
後ろ
What's for rice?
ご飯何?
That's what I'm hearing.
みたいな感じで聞いてる
Would you like to have dinner?
ご飯にする?
Will I?
するかな?
do?
する?
That's what you do.
するんだね
Girls do it too.
女の子もするんだね
So, when do you do that?
それってさ、 どういう時にするの?
When do you want to do it?
どういう時にしたいと思うんですか?
When?
どういう時に?
When you're horny?
ムラムラってした時に?
Are you horny?
ムラムラするの?
ムラムラする?
I won't let you escape.
逃がさないからね
It makes me horny.
ムラムラするんだ
When do you get horny?
どういう時にムラムラするの?
Suddenly?
突発的に?
If I were a man, it would be like I couldn't have sex even if I wanted to.
男だったらさ、 エッチしたくてもできないみたいな感じで エッ
I feel like I want to.
チ したいな、みたいな
It feels like I'm holding back with my hands, and it makes me horny.
手で我慢みたいな感じで ムラムラする
Do girls do it too?
女の子もするかな?
I guess that's probably the case.
多分そうなんじゃないかな
In everyday life, I want to have sex.
日常で生活してて、 エッチしたいな、
Do you think so?
とかって思う?
Tell me, let me be a little horny.
教えて、ちょっとムラムラを代弁して
sometimes?
たまに?
Like, I want to have sex.
エ ッチしたいな、みたいな
But I feel like I don't have anyone to meet.
でも相手いないな、みたいな
It's like holding back a little with your hands.
手 でちょっと我慢みたいな
Feeling.
感じ
What is the end point?
どう が終着点なの?
Girls become women too.
女の子も女に
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
What if I get tired?
疲れたら?
It's like going two or three times and then when you get tired, it's over.
2回、3回行って、疲れたら終わりみたいな
Yeah, I guess?
うん、かな?
That's amazing.
すごいね
Is that the time?
その 時は手?
a little bit...
ちょっと...
Are there many girls?
女の子も多いかな?
女の子も多いんだ?
Do you want to use more?
もっと使う?
What do you use?
何使う?
Reeled?
リールド?
Should I use it already?
もう使うかな?
Something like that?
という感じのやつ?
The one that vibrates?
振動するやつ?
A big one?
大きいやつ?
Something like this Kobame?
この小刃目みたいなやつ?
What does it look like?
どういう感じのやつ?
Womanizer?
ウーマナイザー?
Is it something that vibrates?
なんか振動のやつ?
Chestnut?
栗の?
Hey, you say it feels good, right?
あれ、気持ちいいって言うよね?
That's terrible.
あれやばいんだ
Just hold the vibrator on your phone.
ちょっと電話のバイブを持って
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
How long is the week?
週どれくらいですか?
Oh, I'm sorry.
あ、ごめんなさい
How long is the week?
週どれくらいですか?
Is it okay?
いいかな?
週...
About that much?
そこくらい?
I was really surprised.
めっちゃびっくりした
I've been doing it 1, 2, and 7 times a week.
週1、2、7にしてきた
So, when you turn over, you get horny once or twice a week?
じゃあ、裏返すと週1、2、ムラムラするんですね?
I agree.
そうですね
I'm not letting you escape.
逃がしてませんよ
it is?
それは?
Is it different?
切れ違うかな?
Are you going to say it?
言 っちゃうの?
I might say it.
言っちゃうかも
So, listen to the color.
じゃあ、色を聞いて
My face is turning red.
顔が赤くなってる
My face is turning red though.
顔が赤くなってるんだけど
If you hide the table, it will turn bright red.
台 を隠したら真っ赤になってんじゃん
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
This is something you don't usually hear.
普段聞かれないよね、こういうことね
Sorry, sorry, Delicacy.
ごめんごめん、デリカシーが
Hey, there's a guy who's edgy and irresistible.
ちょっとね、 エッジしたりたまらないという男が チンコイジ
That's what I think.
って 思ってるんで
There's a guy named Chinkoji.
そこにいるんですけど、チンコイジって
Great, because I'm rubbing it.
すげえ、こすことしてるから
But they haven't taken a shower,
でも、彼女たちはシャワー浴びてないから、
I'm going to take a shower.
シャワー浴びてくるからさ
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張しますよ
You did it with me last time.
俺と前回したじゃん
get nervous?
緊張する?
Good, good, good.
いいよいいよ
Not yet.
まだまだ
get nervous?
緊張する?
Feels good.
いい感じ
cute.
かわいい
I'll get ready, so please wait a moment.
準備してくるんで、ちょっと待っておいてね
Relieve your tension.
緊張ほぐしといて
It's really relaxing.
めっちゃリラックスしてるね
nice to meet you.
始めまして
It's really good after all.
全然やっぱりいいですね
It has become a real thing.
実物になってます
terrible,
やばい、
Oh no, no no.
や ばい、やばい
It's bad, it's bad, it's bad.
やばい、やばい、やばい
Sorry.
すいません
I forgot, but
忘れてたんですけど、
Can I start discharging?
デ ィスカル始めてもいいですか?
Realize properly
ちゃんと気づい
That's what I mean.
と る
Amazing, amazing.
すげえ、すげえ